Guide to the Labor Publications and Printed Material Collection, "1861-2011 IBT0001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Union Publications, 1899-2013; Series 5; 6.25 Linear Feet
  - A Hearty Welcome to All Delegates and Friends of the Seventy First Annual Convention of the Connecticut Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO from the Connecticut Federation of Labor, AFL-CIO and Hartford Central Labor Union, 1956 September 25-28; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hell of Herrin Rages Again, 1937; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Help Uncle Sam Win the War by the Shipyard Workers Committee Against Discrimination, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - High Alert 2, 2005; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - High Performance Work and Learning Systems, 1992; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - High Price of Money, December 1973; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - High Road Partnerships Report, Undated; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Higher Salaries More Security Improved Service by Social Service Employees Union, Local 19, 1947 May; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Historical Highlights Of Retail Clerks International Association, 1944; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - History and Philosophy of the Eight-Hour Day Movement by Lemuel Danryid and the American Federation of Labor, 1899; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The History of Labor in New York State, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - History of the U.I.U. by David S. Schick, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - History of Union Labels Shop Cards & Service Buttons by the Union Label and Service Trades Department, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Honest Democratic Unionism vs Enslaving Company Unionism, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Honest Money And Labor, 23 October 1878; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - How Much Sense In A Dollar, 1961; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - How the Union Works by Textile Workers of America, CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - How to Lie Scientifically, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - How to Look at Your Plant by Urban Planning Aid Inc., undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - How to Prevent a Race Riot in Your Hometown by Winifred Raushenbush, 1943 October; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - How to Run a Union Meeting by the American Federation of Labr and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1959; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - How to Speak Effectively by Sid Marquit, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - How to Win: A Handbook for Political Education by the AFL-CIO Committe on Political Education, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - How To Write A Union Flyer, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Humanizing the VDT Workplace, April 1982; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - IBPAT 100th Anniversary Calendar, 1987; Series 5 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    General
    Published by the International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades.
  - If You Work for a Railroad, udated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - If I Were - An Industrial Manager - A Labor Leader, 1944; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - ILO Century Project Ideas, Policies And Progress, 2009; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Important Events In American Labor History, 1778-1971; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - The Incredabile Rocky vs The Power of the People!, 1973; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Index Teamster Press Coverage, January 1972; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Council Anti-Descrimination Committees by George Weaver, 1944 August 16; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Industry Planning Through Collective Barganing by Julius Hochman, the International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, 1914 January; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Industrial Relations And Wage Terms, May 1965; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Industrial Relations Report Wage Incentive Practices, 2 March 1953; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Industrial Unions and Taft-Hartley by Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Industry's Law Against the People by United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Institute Of Industrial Relations Balkanization of Labor Markets, 1954; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Institute of Industrial Relations Trade Unionism And Distributive Shares, 1954; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Institute Of industrial Relations American Trade Unionism, 1961; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Institute Of Industrial Relations Collective Bargaining And Inflation, 1960; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Institute of Industrial Relations Unions and Union Leaders of Their Own Choosing, 1958; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - International Mailer's Union Newsletter, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Introduction To The Work of State Humanities Councils - A Labor Perspective, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - In Harm's Way, 2008; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Development Structure Functions, 1969; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - International Union United by Automobile Workers of America Presents United Action Means Victory, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Inventory Of American Labor Landmarks, Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Israel Labour News, January 1950-July 1953; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Issues in Labor-Management Relations, 1953; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Is There a Crissi in the Labor movement? No, 1959; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - It's Your Right to Join the Union, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Its Up to You by Marine Cooks and Stewards Association - CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - I.W.W. Songs by Industrial Workers of the World, 1939 January; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Jean Maddox: the Fight for Rank and File Democracy by Jean Maddox, Pamela Allen, and Sisters from Local 29, 1976; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - the Jewish Labor Movement in America by Israel Knox and Irving Howe, 1958 May; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Job Description and Classification Manual by United Steel Workers of American AFL-CIO-CLC; Coordinating Committee Steel Companies, 1971 August 1; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Jobs for All After the War: CIO Political Action Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Keep Wages Free for a Free America by Congress of Industrial Organizations, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - La Survivance - Labor In The Blackstone Valley, 1912; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Labor, Big Business And Inflation, September 1958; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Labor Day Review, 1898; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Labor Hall of Fame, 1989; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Labor History and Labor of Today, 27 April 1962; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Labor Management Relations Act of 1947 As Last Amended in 1959, Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Labor Monopolies - Or Freedom, 1946; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Labor Movement In The United States, February 1958; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Laborer - A Century, 2003; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Labor's International Hall of Fame Plaque - Victor Reuther & Elizabeth Gurley-Flynn, 2011; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Labor's International Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony Poster, 2011; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Labor's International Hall of Fame Booklet, "Preserving Labor's History", 17 May, 2011; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Labor's International Hall of Fame Ceremony, 2012; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Labor's International Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony Program, 2013; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Leader, July 2008; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Learn Networker, March 2009; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Lest We Forget, 18 March 1948; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - LGBT Rights and Labor San Francisco Labor Ballot Information, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Life in the Factory, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - List of Publications of the AFL-CIO, 1991; Series 5 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local 18 - international Brotherhood of ELectrical Workers, 1893-1968; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Local Union Golden Volunteer Award, 1986; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Lowell Offering, 1825; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Labor Relations Law, 1979; Series 7 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Labor and the American Way by Mark Starr, 1961; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Labor and Civil Rights by Califronia Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 1959 August 10-14; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Labor Champion of Public Education by Amerian Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1970 November; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Labor Defender by International Labor Defense, 1927 September; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Labor in the New Deal Decade by Selig Perlmann, 1945; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Labor Looks at the 90th Congress by the AFL-CIO Department of Legislation, 1968 December; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Labor Scrapbook by United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Labor Scrap-Book by Education Department United Rubber, Cork, Linoluem and Plastic Workers of AMerica, AFL-CIO, unknown; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Labor's Stake in Abolishing the Poll Tax by International Union Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO), 1943 December; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Labor Today, 1962-1963; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Labor and TVA by Tennessee State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Labor Union Manual on Job Evaluation, 1947; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Laborer: A Century by Laborers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 2003; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Fact Book 89th Congress, 1965; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Manual by State of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations, 1965-1966; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Liberty Under the New Deal bu American Civil Liberties Union, 1934 June; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Little Korea...USA bu Thomas Sanetum, 1954 December 15; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Little Steel Formula by the American Federation of Labor Members of the National War Labor Board, 1944 September 26; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Local 6 in Action by Warehouse Union Local 6, JLWU-CIO, 1947 March; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Local Union Elections Manual by United Steelworkers of America, 1960 March 15; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Local Union Elections Manual by United Steelworkers of America, 1964 January 30; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Local Union Elections Manual by United Steelworkers Manual by United Steelworkers of America, 1965 April 2; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Longshoremen! Sold Out! What Next? by Lee J. Holman, 1936 October 8; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Management Electioneering Guide, Undated; Series 5 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Major BLS Programs - A Summary of Theri Characteristics, 1968; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Marching Workers, 1978; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Maritime Unity by Joseph Curran, 1937 August; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts State Branch of the American Federation bu Labor Eighth Annual Convention, 1893 August 7-9; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - The Media Notebooks, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Membership Wins Again by Joseph Curran, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - A Message to Seamen by International Seamen's Union of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - The Miners Magazine by the Western Federation of Miners, 1911 August 17; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The Miners Magazine by The Western Federation of Miners, 1914 May 21; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Minimum Wages And Hours Data International Typographical Union, July 1985; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Patches, 1981-1984 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Labor History Booklets, 1976-1980 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Missouri Teamster Editorials: For Union Action to End the War in Vietnam by Trade Unionists for Peace, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Montana Report and Labor History, 24-29 June 1984; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Montana State AFL-CIO The Family of Workers, 16-18 August 1984; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - More Than 100 Years Ago, ... The Last Pullman Car, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Mother Jones, Woman Organizer by Priscilla Long, 1976; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - The MTD's: 20 Point Maritime Program by Maritime Trades Department, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Mutual Survival The Goal Of Unions and Management, 1946; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Nation: Taps Bugs and Spies Anything To Get Hoffa, 29 February 1967; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - National Warehouse Division Policy Committee Meetings, 26-30 June 1977; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Needle and Thread 1915-1960 45 Years Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America by New York Joint Board, A.C.W.A., Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - The new England Fisherman, 1997; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - New Towns For Old, 1965; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - New York State AFL-CIO 2001 Labor History Calendar, Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The New York Times Magazine, 15 November 1953; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - N.M.U., n.d.; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - The N.M.U. Answers Congressman Bradley by National Maritime Union of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - The N.M.U. Fights Jim Crow by National Maritime Union, 1943 March; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - The N.M.U. Forges Ahead by Joseph Curran, 1940 January; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - The N.M.U. Manual Political Action by National Maritime Union, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - N.M.U. Ten minute Talks, 30 December 1939; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - North South of the Border by CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - The Occupational Safety And Health Act, Janaury 1976; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - The Oilfields Workers Trade Union July 1937-July 1977 by Oilfields Workers Trade Union, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - On to the Supreme Court! 50 Fired Longshoremen Demand Justice!by Longshoremen Jobs Defense Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - One Hundred Years of American Labor 1881-1981 by AFL-CIO, Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - An Open Letter To All Longshoremen, N.D.; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Organizations affiliated With American Federation of Labor And Congress of Industrial Organixations, 1 March 1956; Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Organizing and the Law, June 2001; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Our History - A Brief Look at Cleveland Labor History int he Downtown Area, June 1986; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Our Jobs, Our Health, Our Lives, Our Fight: Report of the First National Labor Coference for Safe Energy and Full Employment by Labor Committee for Safe Energy and Full Employment, 1980 October; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Our Union Heritage, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Out of the Crucible by United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - The open Shop Movement, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - The Origins Of Left Culture In The US 1880-1940, Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - The PanAfrican Labour Movement/Le Movement Syndical PanAfricain-published by the African Trade Union Confederation, 1965; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Pass the Magnusson- Lesinski Bill!, 1950 January; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Pension Fund - American Association Of Industrial Management, 21 March 1967; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - A Personal History By A Rank And File Worker: The Depression of the Thirties, August 1980; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Petition ... to the United Nations on Behalf of 13 Million Opressed Negro Citizens of the USA, 6 June 1946; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Pictures Tell The Story-Boiler And Machinery Explosions, Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Planning Better Union Meetings by Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Buthcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Political Directions For Labor, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Point Rating Values for Non-Supervisory Factory Jobs in the Screw Machine Products Industry, 20 February 1945; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Portrait of a Union, 1958-1965; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Postal Workers Fight Back, 1975; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Positive Role Of Fiscal Policy, Janaury 1963; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - A Practical but Almost Complete Guide for the Striking College Teacher, 1969 January 15; Series 5 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Progressive Employers Favor Unemployment Reserve Funds, 1930; Series 5 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Profit Sharing, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Professional Flight Attendants Association Newsletter, January 2004; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Program of Laborers for Democracy, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Proud Heritage: A Brief History of the United Steelworkers of America, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Public Employee by American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, 1986 July; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Pursers...Sum It Up! It's N.M.U. for You! bu National Maritime Union, CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Rail Teamsters, 2008; Series 5 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Raising Cane, 1946 September; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rapport D'Activite-8eme Congres National Union Generale Tunisienne du Travail, April 1960; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Rational Industrialization- An Economic Development Agenda for Detroit, 1981; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Rats for Hire! by International Typographical Union, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Real Target by Bridges-Robertson-Schmidt Defense Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Recent Reenactments of the Pennslyvania Workmen's Compensation Laws, February 1940; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Remedy For Industrial Warfare, Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Remembering Where You Came From: A Guide for Labor Leaders by Charles D. Reese and Mark Sullivan E., 1995; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Reprints From Sing Out - The Folk Song Magazine, 1964; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Report of AFL-CIO Delegation to Norther Ireland and the Republican of Ireland by Thomas R. Donahue, John J. Sweeney, and James E. Hatfield, 1983; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Report of the CIO Delegation to the Soviet Union by James B. Carey, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Resolutions-Second Conference of the All-African Trade Union Federation, June 1964; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - A Report on the Special Session of Congress by A.F. Whitney, 1948 July 26 - August 7; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Reports Required Under The LMRDA, 1967; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Response to the Mahoning Valley Steel Crisis, 29 November 1977; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Review, 1984; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Rhode Island AFL-CIO, September 1980; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rhode Island AFL-CIO Labor Studies, September 1980; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Right to Work Laws and the Common Good by Jerome L. Toner, 1959; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Right To Work Is A Bad Law, 27 March 1961; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Right To Work Law, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Rights, 1953 December - 1954 January; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ritual of Subordinate Lodges of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1925; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ritual of Subordinate Lodges of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1947; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The River Rat Murder Case by Aleine Austin, 1945 April; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Rocky Mountain Labor School AFL-CIO, July 1986; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Role of Labor Today by James J. Matles, 1975 September 10; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Roster of 32nd Convention by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1964 September 28; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Roster of First Quadrennial (twenty-sixth) Convention by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1935 May; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Rules For Union Meetings, 1948; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Rules Governing Committees on Political Education of State and Local Central Bodies by AFL-CIO, 1978 February; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Samuel Gompers' "Credo", "In Retrospect", and "Evaluated" by the AFL Samuel Gompers Centennial Committee, 1950; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Save Our State from the Compulsory Open Shop by Los Angeles County Labor Committee, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Shalom: American Unionists in Israel, September 1969; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - The Shop Steward: Key to a Strong Union by URW Education Department, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - A Short History of American Labor, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Sing a Labor Song by the International Association of Machinists, undated; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The SIU at War by Seafarers International Union of North America, 1944 August; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Skyword, Spring 2008; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Skyword, Winter 2007; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Skyword, Summer 2005; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Skyword, Winter 2005; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Skyword, 2004; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Skyword, 1993-2003; Series 5 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - The Slippery Road to Tax Justice, April 1973; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - So! You're In The Union, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Songs of Labor by AFL-CIO Department of Education, 1983 December; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - The Southern Labor Story by Industrial Union Department, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - A State of Emergency In The American Workplace, 18 December 1990; Series 5 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Statements and Reports Adapted by the AFL-CIO Executive Council, 16-23 February 1970; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Steelworkers' case for Wages, Pensions and Social Insurance, 1949; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Steward's Bible, 1954; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Steward's Handbook, Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - St. Louis Labor History, 22-23 October 1994; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Stolen Times - Poems About Production in America, n.d.; Series 5 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Struggle for African Trade Unions, 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Steward's Bible IV, 1946; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "Strike" by Walton H. Craig, 1953; Series 5 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Statement of Purpose, Structure and Guidelines by Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974 March 23-24; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Steady Work, Steady Pay: Questions and Answers about the UAW-CIO Guaranteed Employment Plan by UAW-CIO Education Department, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Steel and Metal Workers - It Takes a Fight to Win! by Gus Hall, 1972 December; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - The Steelworkers' Case for Wages, Pensions, and Social Insurance by Philip Murray, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - The Steward and His Job by Hilton E. Hanna, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Steward's Handbook by Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Stop Runaway Shops by Citizens Labor Committee on Plant Closings, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Storm Over Bridges by Leo Huberman, 1941 September; Series 5 (Box 13, Folder 1)